beachcamera.com 2005-04-07

# Beach Camera

|   
---  

| 

**Privacy Policy  
**  
Beach Camera is firmly committed to the privacy and security of your electronic commerce. For your full understanding, the following statement details how we gather and utilize information, as well as the security measures we take to assure that your information stays secure and private. **Information Collected**  
Beach Camera is committed to protecting your privacy online. Below is a description of how  information is collected from you and how it is used. 

When you shop on our site, we collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password. We may also collect, or our third party ad server and content server will collect the URL you came from, IP address, domain types (e.g. .com or .org, etc.), your browser type, the country, state and telephone area code where your server is located, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit, and any other information regarding the materials you had looked up on our web site. 

**Privacy of Information**  
We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect for the sole purpose of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site, protecting the card holders from fraudulent purchases, serving advertisements, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We may use third parties to help us fulfill orders, to help process payments, to provide customer service, to serve site content, to serve the advertisements you see on our site, to conduct surveys, to help administer promotional emails, to administer warranties purchased, and to administer drawings or contests. We give them access to the information needed to do their job. Sometimes that includes your personal information. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology. **What about cookies**  
We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store and to customize your experience. The cookies contain randomly assigned user identification numbers. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies. We use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they place a separate cookie on your computer. The ad server collects and uses your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad. We do not disclose your personal account information or any information about your purchases to our ad server. **Secured Transactions**  
For credit card transactions, Beach Camera adds security by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. This means that the credit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, preventing others from accessing your private information in between. So, when using an SSL capable browser, shopping on Beach Camera's web site is the safest kind of transaction possible with a credit card. **Other Links**  
We may include links on Beach Camera to other companies’ sites. Beach Camera is not responsible for the privacy policies and content of those sites.

|  |
